<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>http://tinauto.github.io</id>
    <title>Gridea</title>
    <updated>2024-08-27T04:04:44.101Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://tinauto.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="http://tinauto.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>为可爱的小车车拍照</subtitle>
    <logo>http://tinauto.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>http://tinauto.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2024, Gridea</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】雪佛兰 开拓者\Chevrolet Blazer]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-xue-fu-lan-kai-tuo-zhe/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-xue-fu-lan-kai-tuo-zhe/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-08-10T11:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>雪佛兰 开拓者<br>
开拓者SUV最早出现于1969年，它是雪佛兰基于基于C/K系列皮卡系列打造而来的一款三门全尺寸SUV。<br>
1982年，雪佛兰为了应对第二次石油危机和两伊战争所带来的高油价，开发了尺寸更加紧凑、排量更小的的四门SUV S-10 Blazer；1995年，雪佛兰继续推出了S-10 Blazer的第二代车型；</p>
<p>2000年6月,成立于1992年6月的金杯-通用合资公司在第六届北京国际汽车工业展览会上“正式”发布了国产的S-10 Blazer二代型，其中SUV和厢式车被命名为-雪佛兰开拓者，而皮卡版则使用了S-10这一代号作为名称。</p>
<p>2001年首批上市的车型为4.3升V6和2.4升两款，2003年则追加了3.0升V6引擎，也就是君威和GL8上搭载的同款。</p>
<p>2004年2月，上海通用正式收购金杯-通用，后者同时更名为“上海通用(沈阳)北盛汽车有限公司”。<br>
拍摄于2024年8月！</p>
<p>===<br>
Chevrolet Blazer,<br>
The Trailblazer SUV first appeared in 1969 as a three-door full-size SUV based on Chevrolet C/K Pickup.In 1982, Chevrolet developing S-10 Blazer a compact and smaller four-door SUV responded to the second oil crisis and high oil prices caused by the Iran-Iraq War . In 1995, Chevrolet went on to introduce the next generation of the S-10 Blazer;</p>
<p>In June 2000, the Jinbei-GM joint venture which was founded in 1992, &quot;officially&quot; released the domestic S-10 Blazer second generation at the sixth Beijing International Automobile Industry Exhibition, the SUV and pickup-van were named - Chevrolet Blazer, and the pickup version was named S-10 .</p>
<p>The first sales on the market were a 4.3L V6 and a 2.4L in 2001, and a 3.0L V6 engine was added in 2003, the same one found in the Regal and GL8.</p>
<p>In February 2004, Shanghai GM  acquired Jinbei-GM, which was renamed &quot;Shanghai GM (Shenyang) Beisheng Automobile Co., LTD.&quot;.<br>
Shooting in August 2024！</p>
<p>+++<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1723252023171.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1723252043639.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】大众 辉腾\Volkswagen Phaeton]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-da-zhong-hui-teng/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-da-zhong-hui-teng/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-27T10:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>大众 辉腾<br>
1994年上市的第一代A8一举确立了奥迪的作为豪华品牌形象，此时，作为CEO的皮耶希诞生了一个大胆的计划，他期望在利用大众和奥迪同属于大众集团这一优势从而开发出一款悬挂大众标的高端豪华轿车。为了实现这一个目标大众集团甚至在正式开始设计之前就建造了被称为透明工厂的德累斯顿工厂。</p>
<p>遵循资源共享这一原则大众的工程师在第二代A8的D3平台上将全铝车身替换为了高强度钢，重新开发出了D1平台。并以此为基础制定了代号为“3D”的豪华车开发计划，这款车最后定名辉腾(phaeton)。</p>
<p>辉腾于2002年5月正式上市；2002年11月，伴随夏朗登陆中国，德国大众在北京正式成立了进口车业务部；2004年4月20日，大众汽车在德国德累斯顿的透明工厂宣布，辉腾轿车正式投放中国市场。首先在中国销售的辉腾是W12车型，售价为188万人民币。<br>
拍摄于2021年10月！</p>
<p>+++<br>
Volkswagen Phaeton<br>
The first generation A8, which launched  in 1994, established Audi's luxury image. At this time, the CEO Piech, have a bold plan , which plan was use the group’s resources bwtween VW and Audi to develop a VW-badged premium car ,for the project ,the company even built a showcase factory for the car before it had even been designed: the so-called ‘glass factory’ in Dresden which now turns out VW’s hybrid models.</p>
<p>Follow the 1 principles of resource sharing，engineers built the vw ‘D1’ platform on the Audi A8 d3 platform and replaced the all-aluminum body with high-strength steel. Based on this, he developed a plan for the development of a luxury car code-named &quot;3D&quot;, which was eventually named the phaeton.</p>
<p>The Phaeton was launched in 2002; In November 2002, with the Sharan selling in China, Volkswagen officially established the import car business department in Beijing; On April 20, 2004, Volkswagen announced  in Dresden, that the Phaeton was officially launched in the Chinese market. The first Phaeton sold in China is W12 model and priced at 1.88 million Yuan.<br>
Shooting in October 2021!</p>
<p>===<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1722079484094.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1722079491348.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】新龙马-启腾EX80\New Longma-Qiteng EX80]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-fu-jian-long-ma/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-fu-jian-long-ma/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-13T11:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>启腾EX80<br>
新龙马前身是老龙马，而老龙马的前身则是福建龙岩龙马拖拉机厂，该厂始建于1970年，主要产品是手扶拖拉机拖斗及小型农机。上世纪90年代，龙岩拖拉机厂看到市场上农用车需求量大这个空当，率先在全国制造出内质是拖拉机、外面却有玻璃挡风和方向盘的第一代龙马农用车（变型拖拉机）。1999年12月30日，龙马集团与福建汽车厂正式签订合同，由龙马集团正式兼并福建汽车厂，从此龙马汽车获得了汽车生产目录。</p>
<p>2000年后龙马拖拉机厂因经营不善关门歇业，2003年与福汽重组，并将“龙马”汽车重新命名为“新龙马”；新龙马2003~2012年因长期停产或半停产，持续处于亏损状态。2014年新龙马发布启腾品牌，先后推出了微客M70、MPV-EX80、SUV-V60。而到了2016年，新龙马汽车被国能电动车（NEVS）重组，后者及其关联公司持股比例达到65%、福汽集团占20%、龙马汽车占比15%。</p>
<p>而后随着国能电动车在2019年被恒大汽车收购，其与新龙马的合作也宣告结束。然而，随着恒大集团陷入重度财务违约其也不得不走上卖股的道路。最终，福汽集团持股53.915%，龙岩投资集团持有43.347%，新龙马重新回到福汽集团旗下。<br>
拍摄于2024年6月！</p>
<p>+++<br>
Qiteng EX80<br>
The predecessor of the new Longma is old Longma, and the predecessor of the old Longma is the Fujian Longyan Longma Tractor Factory, which was founded in 1970, the main products are &quot;Walking tractor&quot; and simple agricultural machine. In the 1990s, Longyan Tractor Factory saw the chance in the market demand for agricultural vehicles, and producing the Longma agricultural vehicles which used tractor chassis and a Fully enclosed comfortable cockpit. On December 30, 1999, Longma Group officially signed a contract with Fujian Automobile Factory, and Longma Group officially annexed Fujian Automobile Factory, from this annexed Longma Automobile obtained the automobile production licence.</p>
<p>After 2000, Longma tractor factory bankrupt due to poor management, and restructured with Fujian Automobile Group in 2003, meanwhile , Longma renamed &quot;New Longma&quot; .  New Longma continued fall into state of loss management and  long-term production full or half shutdown from 2003 to 2012. In 2014, the new Longma launched Qiteng brand, and several vehicles such as the minivan M70, MPV-EX80, and SUV-V60. In 2016, the “New Longma” was restructured by the National Energy Electric Vehicle (NEVS), NEVS and affiliates held 65% shares of new company, Fujian Auto Group accounting 20% and New Longma  accounting 15%.</p>
<p>Then, with the acquisition of NEVS by Evergrande Automobile in 2019, cooperation betwen NEVS  New Longma also came to an end. However, as Evergrande Group fell into severe financial default, it had to embark on the road of selling shares. In the end, Fujian Auto Group held 53.915%, Longyan Investment Group held 43.347%, and New Longma returned to the Fujian Auto Group.<br>
Shooting in June 2024!</p>
<p>===<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1722173733405.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1722173740126.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】煤老板的汽车梦-成功汽车\Automobile dream of coal boss-Vtctory Auto]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-mei-lao-ban-de-qi-che-meng-cheng-gong-v1/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-mei-lao-ban-de-qi-che-meng-cheng-gong-v1/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-06-22T10:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>成功汽车<br>
1990年10月，从部队复员的马国利，在山西长治当地开始了自己的煤炭生意。8年之后，31岁的马国利创建了山西成功煤炭经销有限公司，他旗下的联盛公司在巅峰时期拥有7座煤矿、K18BK自备车两列（97节）、KM70自备车一列、铁路煤炭集运站3个。</p>
<p>随着2001中国加入wto，中国国内制造业高速发展，对于能源的需求随即大幅增加，煤炭价格也一路走高。但是，随之而来的就是煤炭事故频发，在此背景之下山西开始大刀阔斧的煤企改革之路，煤老板们纷纷转型。他们中有的选择白酒、有的选择农业，而马国利则选择汽车行业。</p>
<p>2006年5月，成功集团收购淮海发动机；2008年6月，成功集团通过收购贵州航天汽车，拿到了微面生产目录和遵义生产基地；2010年8月6日晚，成功集团在内蒙古呼伦贝尔市举办了“成功一号”上市发布会，因为此时成功汽车山西太行工厂还未建成，所以成功一号的尾标依旧使用的是“航天汽车+成功一号”的组合；2013年山西太行工厂建成之后，“航天汽车+成功一号”也就变成了“成功汽车+v1”。<br>
拍摄于2024年6月！</p>
<p>+++<br>
Victory Auto<br>
In October 1990, Ma Guoli, demobilized from the Army, started his coal business in Changzhi, Shanxi. Eight years later, at the age of 31, Ma Guoli founded Shanxi Victory Coal Distribution Co., LTD., at its peak, his Liansheng company owned seven coal mines, two K18BK coal hopper trains, one KM70 coal hopper, and three  freight station.</p>
<p>With China jointo WTO in 2001, the domestic manufacturing industry developed rapidly, and the demand for energy increased sharply, as result，coal prices soared. However, with the frequent occurrence of coal accidents, Shanxi began a drastic reform of coal company，under this background, coal bosses have been transformed. Some of them choose Chinese Baijiu（Chinese liquor）, others choose agriculture, while Ma Guoli chose the automobile.</p>
<p>In May 2006, Victory Group acquired Huaihai Engine company; In June 2008, Victory Group got the minivan production license and Zunyi poduction base through the acquisition of Guizhou Aerospace Automobile; On the evening of August 6 2010, Victory Group held the &quot;Victory 1&quot; launched conference in Hulunbuir Inner Mongolia,  the Victory 1 label still uses the combination of &quot;航天汽车+成功一号&quot; at this time because the license have not move to Victory group ; After the Shanxi Taihang Factory and license moved was completedin 2013, the &quot;航天汽车+成功一号&quot; became &quot;成功汽车+v1&quot;.<br>
Shooting in June 2024!</p>
<p>===<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1719054511235.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1719054517572.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】英菲尼迪G37s\Infiniti G37s]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-ying-fei-ni-di-g37-coupe/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-ying-fei-ni-di-g37-coupe/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-06-08T11:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>英菲尼迪g37s<br>
2007年7月，英菲尼迪在诞生18年之后正式进入中国，其首先带来的是g35（vq35）和fx35\45，加上2004年来的雷克萨斯、2006年来的讴歌，日系三大豪华品牌正式开启了对于中国市场的争夺。<br>
2007年纽约车展上，英菲尼迪发布了g35的升级产品，采用VQ37 3.7L V6发动机动力系统的G37系列取代了之前的G35系列。2008年12月18日，英菲尼迪G37三厢和双门版正式在国内上市，Infiniti G37 双门跑车售价为人民币66万元人民币。另外，G37四门版轿车车型也公布了售价为48.3万元。<br>
拍摄于2024年6月！</p>
<p>btw：英菲尼迪G37是自上个世纪90年代M30敞篷以来英菲尼迪生产的第二款敞篷车也是首辆挂上英菲尼迪车标的敞篷跑车（m30只有尾标而没有前标）</p>
<p>===<br>
Infiniti G37s<br>
In July 2007, Infiniti officially entered China after 18 years of birth, which first brought G35 (vq35) and FX35\45 into China,  In addition with Lexus which 2004 and Acura which 2006, the three Japan luxury brands opened the competition in Chinese market.<br>
At the New York Auto Show 2007, Infiniti launched upgrade of the G35, G37 series which with the VQ37 3.7L V6 engine replacing the previous VQ35 series . On December 18 2008, the Infiniti G37 coupe and sedan were officially launched in China, and the Infiniti G37 coupe was priced at 660,000 Yuan. the sedan was at a price of 483,000 Yuan.<br>
Shooting in June 2024!</p>
<p>btw:G37 is the second cabriolet by Infiniti since the M30 cabriolet in the 1990s, and the first cabriolet to use the Infiniti front logo (the m30 has a rear logo only).</p>
<p>+++<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1718967325133.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>左后\Left rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1718967342020.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】标致607\Peugeot 607]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-biao-zhi-607/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-biao-zhi-607/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-05-25T13:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>标致607<br>
2002年10月，东风集团与法国PSA集团签定了扩大合作的协议，东风-psa公司正式宣告成立。按照标致-雪铁龙与东风达成的协议,从2004年起,神龙公司开始生产标致307轿车（早期只有307三厢版，这是针对中国和土耳其市场的特供车），这意味着标致汽车在广州标致倒闭5年之后重返中国市场。而在307国产之前的这一段空档内标致也没有歇着，标致将的206cc、307cc、406coupe、607以进口方式引入到了国内。</p>
<p>标致607是一款源于标致605/雪铁龙XM平台开发而来的车型，在当时与奔驰E级宝马5系互为竞品。中国市场曾经销售销售过2004版和2006版两个版本，2004年款有2.2升L4与3.0升V6两个版本，售价在43万和47万；2006年推出的则只有3.0升V6一款，售价为47万元。<br>
拍摄于2021年4月！</p>
<p>+++<br>
Peugeot 607<br>
In October 2002, China Dongfeng Group and France PSA Group signed an agreement to expand cooperation area, Dongfeng-Psa company was officially established. According to the agreement , from 2004, Dongfeng-Shenlong began to produce the Peugeot 307 sedan (early only the 307 seden, which was a special for the Chinese and Turkish ), which meant that Peugeot returned to the Chinese market after the Guangzhou Peugeot collapse five years ago. Peugeot did not rest in the gap year before 307 “produing”, and Peugeot introduced 206cc, 307cc, 406coupe and 607 into China by import tunel.</p>
<p>This Peugeot 607 was developed on the Peugeot 605/ Citroen XM platform and was a competitor to the Benz E-Class and BMW 5 Series .Two versions， 2004 and 2006， have been sold in the Chinese market. In 2004 vision, there are two engine 2.2 L4 and 3.0 V6, priced at 430,000 Yuan and 470,000 Yuan. In 2006, only a 3.0 V6 engine, priced at 470,000 Yuan.<br>
Shooting in April 2021！</p>
<p>===<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1716635388209.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>左后\Left rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1716635415375.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】最后的力帆-X80\ The last Lifan-X80]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-zui-da-de-andzui-hou-de-li-fan-x80/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-zui-da-de-andzui-hou-de-li-fan-x80/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>力帆-X80<br>
从2003年力帆发布第一款汽车-力帆520到2020年正式被吉利收购，力帆汽车在17年的生涯里一共生产过两厢车、三厢车、suv、mpv、面包车、封闭货车、微型卡车，甚至还有轻重和重型卡车（力帆通过与大理骏马集团合资）。</p>
<p>而X80则是力帆推出的最后一款车，该车首发于2016年的广州车展，并于 2017年3月在重庆正式上市销售。该车全系均为7座设计，动力为2.0T涡轮增压发动机，共推出5款车型，售价区间为10.99-14.99万元。但是不幸的是，这款力帆给予厚望的车型销量却是十分的惨淡，其<u><em><a href="https://xl.16888.com/s/126949-1.html">月销量</a></em></u>长期稳定在两位数甚至个位数。最终，这款车和力帆一起走下了历史的舞台！<br>
拍摄于2024年5月！</p>
<p>btw：力帆还曾在2019年推出过820的纯电动版，不过这辆车纯粹就是使用15年发布的820燃油版进行的“油改电”所以算不上“最后的力帆”。</p>
<p>+++<br>
Lifan-X80<br>
From 2003, when Lifan released its first car-Lifan 520, to 2020, acquired by Geely, Lifan has produced hatchback、sedan、suv、mpv、minivan、cargo van、mini truck, and even light and heavy trucks (through a joint venture with Dali Junma Group) in its 17 Years career.</p>
<p>The X80 as “the”, which launched at the 2016 Guangzhou Auto Show and sale in Chongqing in March 2017. The car is a seven-seat mid-size suv , power by 2.0T engine, total of 5 models, the price range of 109,900 to 149,900 Yuan. But unfortunately,  the sales data of X80 , which Lifan have high hopes for, is very bleak.The <u><em><a href="https://xl.16888.com/s/126949-1.html">mounth sales data</a></em></u>stability in the double digits  long-term, some mouth even single digits. In the end, this car and Lifan went down the stage of history together!<br>
Shooting in May 2024!</p>
<p>btw: In 2019, Lifan was launched 820 electric vision, but this car is purely a &quot;fuel conversion&quot;, it using the 820 fuel version released in 2015, so it is not the truly&quot;Last Lifan&quot;.</p>
<p>===<br>
左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1715425353621.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1715425376372.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】Shine ISUZU 600P]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-shine-600p/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-shine-600p/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-04-27T07:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A Shine ISUZU 600P Rollback Truck</p>
<p>Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1714204962474.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】比速 T3 \BISU T3]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-bi-su/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-bi-su/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-04-13T03:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>比速 T3<br>
在上世纪初，重庆摩托车产业乘着改革开放的东风曾经风头无限，被戏称为“重庆摩托帮”的三大（力帆、宗申、隆鑫）、三小（银翔、鑫源、渝安） 产销量在2002年时曾一度占国内市场的2/3、占出口市场的1/2。不过，随着之后中国摩托车败走东南亚，再加上国内多地“禁摩”，重庆摩托车产业急转直下。</p>
<p>这些摩托车企业也没有“等死”，而是纷纷寻找生存之策，他们中的四家企业先后走上了相同的道路-“摩转汽”！而银翔正是继力帆（力帆汽车-2003年）、渝安（东风小康-2003年）和鑫源（华晨鑫源\斯威汽车-2008年）之后，第四家涉足汽车制造领域摩托车品牌。</p>
<p>2010年，银翔与当时的国内五大汽车北京汽车集团合作成立北汽银翔汽车。北汽银翔于2012年开始生产威旺面包车和轻型货车，真正让它脱颖而出的是2014年3月推出的幻速S3，其第一年销量就达15万辆。在这一背景之下，重庆银翔认为可以创立一个属于自己的汽车品牌并且复制幻速的成功经验，于是在2015年4月28日银翔正式设立比速汽车。</p>
<p>2016年末，成立一年的比速汽车就推出比速T5、T3、M3三款车型。为了打响品牌知名度，比速邀请黄晓明、吉克隽逸、邓紫棋、范玮琪等明星为其站台。但是现实总比梦想更残酷，比速的销量并不如预期，T5、T3、M3的月均销量最高也没有超过3000辆，最终于2018年7月以一纸“停工待产通知”结束了自己短命生涯！<br>
拍摄于2023年1月1日！</p>
<p>+++<br>
BISU T3<br>
At the beginning of the last century, with the openning and reforming, Chongqing motorcycle industry was been unlimited, in 2002 ,the production and sales of the three big (Lifan, Zongshen, Longxin) and three small (Yinxiang, Xinyuan, Yü&quot;an)  which so called &quot;Chongqing motorcycle gang&quot;  together once accounted for 2/3 of the domestic market, and 1/2 of the export market. However, with the failure of Chinese motorcycles in Southeast Asia, and the &quot;ban moto political &quot; in many city in China, Chongqing's motorcycle industry has turned sharply downward.</p>
<p>These motorcycle companies did not &quot;wait for death&quot;, but try to find ways to survive, four of them have embarked on the same road - &quot;Moto To Auto&quot;! Yinxiang is the last fourth motorcycle brand involved in automobile manufacturing after Lifan (Lifan Automobile -2003), Yü&quot;an (DFSK -2003) and Xinyuan (HuaChen Xinyuan \ SWM Automobile -2008).</p>
<p>In 2010, Yinxiang established BAIC-Yinxiang with Beijing Automobile Group. Baic- Yinxiang started production Weiwang brand mini vans and light truck in 2012, and what really set it apart was the &quot;Huansu S3&quot;, which sold 150,000 units in its first year after launched in March 2014. In this context, Yinxiang believes that it can create a car brand of its own and replicate the successful experience of Huansu. So, on April 28 2015, Yinxiang officially set up &quot;BISU&quot; brand.</p>
<p>At the end of 2016, Bisu launched Bisu T5、T3、M3 . In order to start the brand awareness, BISU invented Huang Xiaoming、Jike Junyi、G.E.M., Fan Wei Qi and other stars as product spokesperson. However, the reality is always more cruel than the dream, the sales solwer than expected, the highest monthly sales of T5, T3, M3 did not more than 3,000, and finally in July 2018 with a paper &quot;work stoppage notice&quot; ended his short life!<br>
Shooting in January 1, 2023!</p>
<p>===<br>
右前\Right front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1713179064535.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1713179072394.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【老旧车】20岁长安CM8\An 20 years old Changan CM8]]></title>
        <id>http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-20-sui-de-lao-ye-ye-chang-an-cm8/</id>
        <link href="http://tinauto.github.io/post/lao-jiu-che-20-sui-de-lao-ye-ye-chang-an-cm8/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-03-30T04:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>长安CM8<br>
2004年6月的在北京国际汽车展上，长安汽车推出了“长安CM8”、概念跑车“龙腾”、概念轿车“长江鲟”三款汽车，其中的CM8作为长安第一款自主开发、具有自主知识产权的自主品牌汽车一出场就赢得了很高的关注，这款车正式结束了长安只有合资（长安铃木、长安福特）和仿制车型（长安之星面包车、st110仿制自铃木carry）的历史。<br>
拍摄于2024年3月！</p>
<p>+++<br>
Changan CM8<br>
In June 2004, at the Beijing International Automotive Exhibition, Changan launched three car -&quot;Changan CM8&quot; the concept sports car &quot;Longteng&quot;, the concept car &quot;Yangtze Sturgeon&quot; , of which CM8 as Changan's first self-developed, with independent intellectual property rights of the independent brand car has got high attention. This car officially ended Changan's history which only have joint ventures models (Changan Suzuki, Changan Ford) and imitation models (Changan Star minivan, st110 copied from Suzuki carry).<br>
Shooting in March 2024!</p>
<p>===<br>
长安CM8的广告片\Advertising of Changan CM8<br>
<a href="https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV1Xi4y1T7G7/">https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV1Xi4y1T7G7/</a></p>
<p>左前\Left front<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1711796095077.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p>右后\Right rear<br>
<img src="http://tinauto.github.io/post-images/1711796102423.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>